Guide to the AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council records, 1935-1978; 1962-1976; 0450-003; 62.97 cubic feet 63 boxes
  - WASHINGTON STATE LABOR COUNCIL, AD HOC COMMITTEE RECORDS, SERIES X
    - Washington Industrial Safety and Health Act (WISHA) Monitoring Committee, Subseries G
      - Miscellaneous, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 54/15)
  - GOVERNMENT AGENCIES, SERIES XI
    - Washington State Government Agencies, Subseries A
      - Washington Comprehensive Health Planning Advisory Council, Sub-Subseries 1
        - General Correspondence, 1967-1976 (Box-folder 54/16)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 54/17)
        - Reports, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 54/18)
        - Miscellaneous, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 54/19)
      - Washington Comprehensive Health Planning Advisory Council, Federal Price Commission Advisory Board for Institutional Health Care Costs, Sub-Subseries 2
        - General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 54/20-54/21)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1972 (Box-folder 54/22)
        - Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 54/23)
      - Washington Ecological Commission, Sub-Subseries 3
        - Organization
          - Appointments - Administration, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 54/24)
          - "Washington Ecology Department" - Elisabeth H. Haskell, 1973 (Box-folder 54/25)
        - General Correspondence, 1967-1977 (Box-folder 54/26-54/31, 55/1-3)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 55/4-55/9)
        - Reports, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 55/10-55/14)
          - "List of Current Reports", 1973-1977 (Box-folder 55/15-55/17)
        - Statements, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 55/18-55/20)
        - Testimony, 1976 (Box-folder 55/21)
        - Legislation, 1976 (Box-folder 55/22-55/27)
        - News Releases, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 56/1-56/2)
        - Miscellaneous, 1967-1976 (Box-folder 56/3-56/8)
        - Subject File - Advice and Guidance Requests, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 56/9-56/16)
      - Washington Ecology Department Director, Selection Committee, Sub-Subseries 4
        - General Correspondence, 1970, 1972 (Box-folder 56/17)
        - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box-folder 56/18)
      - Washington Ecology Department, Model Litter Control Act Committee (Ad Hoc), 1971-1978; Sub-Subseries 5 (Box-folder 56/19)
      - Washington Governor, Civil Defense Advisory Council, Sub-Subseries 6
        - General Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 56/20)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1962 (Box-folder 56/21)
        - Reports, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 56/22)
        - Newsletters, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 56/23)
        - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 56/24)
      - Washington Governor, Commission on the Status of Women, 1962-1968; Sub-Subseries 7 (Box-folder 56/25)
      - Washington Governor, Emergency Resources Planning Commission, 1963-1966; Sub-Subseries 8 (Box-folder 56/26)
      - Washington Governor, Emergency Resources Planning Commission Telecommunications Task Force, 1963-1964; Sub-Subseries 9 (Box-folder 56/27)
      - Washington Governor, Employment of the Handicapped Committee, Sub-Subseries 10
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1977 (Box-folder 56/28)
        - Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box-folder 56/29)
      - Washington Governor, Housing Task Force, 1969; Sub-Subseries 11 (Box-folder 56/30)
      - Washington Governor, Nuclear Energy Advisory Commission, 1969-1972; Sub-Subseries 12 (Box-folder 56/31)
      - Washington Governor, State Planning Advisory Council, 1970-1973; Sub-Subseries 13 (Box-folder 56/32)
      - Washington Governor, Urban Affairs Advisory Council, Sub-Subseries 14
        - General Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 56/33)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 56/34)
        - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box-folder 57/1)
      - Washington Health Department, Medicare Advisory Council, 1966-1978; Sub-Subseries 15 (Box-folder 57/2)
      - Washington Interagency Council On Smoking and Health, 1971-1973; Sub-Subseries 16 (Box-folder 57/3)
      - Washington Citizen's Highway Safety Advisory Committee, Sub-Subseries 17
        - General Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 57/4)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 57/5)
        - Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 57/6)
      - Washington Legislature, Judicial Article Task Force, Sub-Subseries 18
        - General Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 57/7)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 57/8-57/16)
        - Legislation, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 57/17-57/18)
      - Washington Public Assistance Department, Statewide Work Relief Committee, Sub-Subseries 19
        - General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 57/19)
        - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box-folder 57/20)
      - Washington Public Employees Collective Bargaining Committee, Sub-Subseries 20
        - General Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 57/21-57/22)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 57/23-57/24)
        - Legislation, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 57/25)
        - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box-folder 57/26)
      - Washington Social and Health Services Department Advisory Committee, Sub-Subseries 21
        - General Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 57/27-57/28)
        - Minutes and Agenda, Undated (Box-folder 57/29)
        - Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 58/1-58/4)
      - Washington Social and Health Services Department, Alcoholism Advisory Council, Sub-Subseries 22
        - General Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 58/5-58/6)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 58/7)
        - Legislation, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 58/8)
        - Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 58/9)
        - Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 58/10)
      - Washington Social and Health Services Department, Hospital and Medical Services Advisory Committee, Sub-Subseries 23
        - General Correspondence, 1958-1974, Undated (Box-folder 58/11-58/12)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1961-1973 (Box-folder 58/13)
        - Speeches and Writings, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 58/14)
        - Miscellaneous, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 58/15-58/16)
      - Washington Social and Health Services Department, Washington Economic Test Advisory Group (West), 1974; Sub-Subseries 24 (Box-folder 58/17)
      - Washington State University, Vocational Education Research Project, 1965-1966; Sub-Subseries 25 (Box-folder 58/18)
      - Washington Teacher Education Advisory Committee, 1969-1971; Sub-Subseries 26 (Box-folder 58/19)
      - Washington United Job Corps Committee, Sub-Subseries 27
        - Organization, 1964 (Box-folder 58/20)
        - General Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 58/21-58/24)
        - Interoffice Correspondence, 1964 (Box-folder 58/25-58/27)
        - Reports
          - United Job Corps Committee Manual, 1964 (Box-folder 58/28)
          - Public Report: "Project: Job Corps", 1964 (Box-folder 58/29)
        - News Releases, 1964 (Box-folder 59/1)
        - Clippings, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 59/2)
        - Ephemera, 1964 (Box-folder 59/3)
        - Subject File - "Let's Go to Work"
          - Campaign Kit, 1964 (Box-folder 59/4)
        - Subject File - Job Corps Survey, 1964 (Box-folder 59/5)
      - University of Washington, Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Institute, Community Advisory Board, Sub-Subseries 28
        - General Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 59/6)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1974 (Box-folder 59/7)
        - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box-folder 59/8)
      - University of Washington, Public Health and Community Medicine School Visiting Committee, Sub-Subseries 29
        - General Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 59/9)
        - Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box-folder 59/10)
    - Seattle-King County, Subseries B
      - Seattle Model Cities, Legal Economics Design Project, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 59/11)
    - United States Government, Subseries C
      - United States Agriculture Department, Snoqualmie National Forest Advisory Council, 1970-1972; Sub-Subseries 1 (Box-folder 59/12)
      - United States Bonneville Power Regional Advisory Council, 1970-1978; Sub-Subseries 2 (Box-folder 59/13)
      - United States Labor Department, Washington State Manpower Advisory Committee, Sub-Subseries 3
        - General Correspondence, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 59/14-59/15)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 59/16-59/17)
        - News Releases, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 59/18)
        - Miscellaneous, 1961-1971 (Box-folder 59/19-59/21)
        - Subject File - Camps (Cooperative Area Manpower Planning Systems), 1971 (Box-folder 59/22)
        - Subject File - Comprehensive Manpower Plan, FY 1971, Parts A and B (Box-folder 59/23-59/24)
        - Subject File - Committee Appointment, 1963 (Box-folder 59/25)
        - Subject File - Membership Lists, 1969 (Box-folder 59/26)
        - Subject File - Washington State Manpower Coordinating Committee, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 59/27)
      - United States Labor Department, Western States Regional Manpower Advisory Committee, Sub-Subseries 4
        - General Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 59/28-59/29)
        - Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 59/30, 60/1)
        - Subject File - National Manpower Advisory Committee Manpower Development and Training Act, 1962 (Box-folder 60/2)
        - Subject File - National Manpower Advisory Committee Manpower Development and Training Act, 1969 (Box-folder 60/3)
      - United States President, Consumer Affairs Office, Consumer Interest Committee, 1964-1971; Sub-Subseries 5 (Box-folder 60/4)
  - OTHER ORGANIZATIONS, SERIES XII
    - Citizens Conference on State Legislatures, Subseries A
      - General Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 60/5)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box-folder 60/6-60/7)
      - Subject File - Model Committee Staff Project Legislator Orientation and Staff Training Seminars, 1974 (Box-folder 60/8)
    - Committee for a New Tax Policy for Washington State, Steering Committee, 1971; Subseries B (Box-folder 60/9)
    - Committee for Agricultural Workers Legislation, 1967-1969; Subseries (Box-folder 60/10)
    - Committee for Washington Tax Reform, Subseries C
      - General Correspondence, 1965-1968, Undated (Box-folder 60/11)
      - Speeches and Writings, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 60/12)
      - Clippings, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 60/13)
      - News Releases, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 60/14)
      - Miscellaneous, 1967-1918 (Box-folder 60/15)
    - Consumer Federation of America, Subseries D
      - General Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 60/16-60/17)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 60/18)
    - Forward Thrust, Inc. Committee of 200, 1966-1969; Subseries E (Box-folder 60/19)
    - Keep Washington Green Association, 1957-1959; Subseries F (Box-folder 60/20)
    - Northwest Rural Opportunities Council, Area II - General Correspondence, 1970; Subseries G (Box-folder 60/21)
    - Seattle Children's Home, Subseries H
      - Organization, 1963-1965, Undated (Box-folder 60/22)
      - General Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 60/23-60/25)
      - Interoffice Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 60/26-60/27)
      - Minutes and Agenda - Board of Trustees, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 60/28-60/30)
      - Financial Records, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 60/31-60/32)
      - Reports, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 60/33)
      - Ephemera, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 60/34)
    - Washington Citizens' Council of The National Council On Crime and Delinquency, Subseries I
      - General Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 61/1-61/2)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 61/3)
      - Speeches and Writings, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 61/4)
      - Conferences and Conventions - United Good Neighbors Budget Conference, 1965 (Box-folder 61/5)
      - Miscellaneous, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 61/6)
    - Washington Coalition for a National Health Program, Subseries J
      - Organization, 1975 (Box-folder 61/7)
      - General Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 61/8-61/9)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 61/10)
      - Speeches and Writings, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 61/11)
      - Newsletters, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 61/12)
      - Miscellaneous, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 61/13)
    - Washington Environmental Council, Subseries K
      - General Correspondence, 1963-1978 (Box-folder 61/14-61/15)
      - Minutes and Agenda
        - Board of Directors, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 61/16-61/17)
        - Executive Committee, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 61/18)
      - Speeches and Writings, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 61/19)
      - Newsletters, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 61/20)
      - Conferences and Conventions, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 61/21)
      - Ephemera, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 61/22)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 61/23)
    - Washington Power Users Association, 1965-1967; Subseries L (Box-folder 61/24)
    - Washington State International Trade Fair, Subseries M
      - General Correspondence, 1953-1972 (Box-folder 61/25)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1953-1971 (Box-folder 61/26)
      - Reports, 1957-1972 (Box-folder 61/27)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954-1971 (Box-folder 61/28)
    - Washington Welcome, Inc., Subseries N
      - General Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 62/1)
      - Interoffice Correspondence, 1963 (Box-folder 62/2)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1963 (Box-folder 62/3)
      - Reports, 1962 (Box-folder 62/4)
      - Ephemera, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - Western Environmental Trade Association, Subseries O
      - General Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 62/6)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Western Shipbuilders Association, Subseries P
      - General Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 62/8-62/9)
      - Bulletins, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 62/10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 62/11)
    - Western Washington Committee for Expo '74, Subseries Q
      - General Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 62/12)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 62/13)
      - Financial Records, 1974 (Box-folder 62/14)
      - News Releases, 1974 (Box-folder 62/15)
      - Newsletters, 1974 (Box-folder 62/16)
      - Ephemera, 1974 (Box-folder 62/17)
  - AUDIO RECORDINGS, SERIES XIII
    - Audio Tapes, 1949, Undated; Subseries A; 39 sound tape reels .5 inches; 4 recording wires (Box-folder 63)
      None are identified.
    - Audio Logs, Subseries B
      - Labor Day Message, George Meany, 1956 (Box:oversize Disc 2)
      - Image of History, 20 Years of the C.I.O., narrated By Melvyn Douglas, Undated (Box:oversize Disc 2)
      - Senator Kennedy Speaks, COPE (AFL-CIO), Undated (Box:oversize Disc 2)
      - Vote No on 202 (Right to Work) AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box:oversize Disc 2)
      - United Labor Advisory Commission Against Initiative 202, 30 second spots, 1958 (Box:oversize Disc 2)
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council records, 1958-1981; 1971-1978; 0450-005; 12 cubic feet 12 boxes
  Arranged in original order as received from donor.
  Correspondence, legislation, conferences, subject series, case files. Subject files also include correspondence. Of particular significance are materials relating to the Council’s Committee on Political Education’s consumer protection activities between 1969 and 1975.
  Case files in box 3 restricted.
  Gift of AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council, March 22, 1982.
  - OUTGOING LETTERS OF EDUCATION DIRECTOR, 1975-1976, 1979-1980; SERIES I (Box-folder 1)
  - OUTGOING LETTERS OF RESEARCH DIRECTOR, 1980-1981; SERIES II
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, SERIES III
    - Congressional delegation
      - McCormack, Mike, 1954, 1971-1980 (Box-folder 1)
      - Magnuson, Warren G., 1976-1980 (Box-folder 1)
  - INTEROFFICE CORRESPONDENCE(CENTRAL LABOR COUNCILS, TRADE COUNCILS), circa 1953, 1970-1978; SERIES IV (Box-folder 2)
  - LEGISLATION, 1974-1979; SERIES V (Box-folder 2)
  - CONFERENCES, SERIES VI
    - General, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 3)
    - WSLC biennial, 1976, 1980 (Box-folder 3)
  - SUBJECT FILES, 1958, circa 1973-1980; SERIES VII (Box-folder 3)
  - INDUSTRIAL INSURANCE-INDIVIDUAL CASES, Undated; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 3)
    Restricted.
  - PRESIDENT JOE DAVIS PAPERS, SERIES IX
    - Legislation
      - D. L. Ray, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 4)
      - Unemployment compensation, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 4)
    - Executive board, 1963-1977 (Box-folder 4)
  - EDUCATION DIRECTOR LOUIS O. STEWART'S PAPERS, SERIES X
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 4)
    - Report, United Labor Lobby, 1979 (Box-folder 4)
    - Legislation, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 4)
    - Subject files, A-P, Undated (Box-folder 5)
    - Subject files, T-Y, Undated (Box-folder 6)
    - Washington Trade, Industrial and Technical Education, State Advisory Committee, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 6)
    - Washington Vocational Education, Statewide Advisory Committee, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 6)
  - RESEARCH DIRECTOR LAWRENCE KENNY'S PAPERS, SERIES XI
  - SUBJECT FILES - KING-SNOHOMISH MANPOWER CONSORTIUM, 1979; SERIES XII (Box-folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO, POLITICAL ACTION COMMITTEE (COPE), SERIES XIII
    - Miscellaneous legislative files, 1966, 1971-circa 1977 (Box-folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous legislative files, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 7)
    - Conferences
      - Workshops, 1966, 1975 (Box-folder 7)
      - Statewide Endorsement Conventions, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 7)
    - Subject file: Consumer Protection
      - A-Air Travel, circa 1969-1975 (Box-folder 7)
      - Auto-Debt, circa 1969-1975 (Box-folder 8)
      - Door-G, circa 1969-1975 (Box-folder 9)
      - H-No-Fault, circa 1969-1975 (Box-folder 10)
      - Nu-W, circa 1969-1975 (Box-folder 11)
  - FEDERATED AMERICAN INSURANCE COMPANY, Undated; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 12)
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council records, 1946-1982; 0450-006; 13.6 cubic feet 13 boxes
  Correspondence, minutes, legislative files, newsletters, conferences and conventions, 1946-1982.
  Gift of AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council, Olympia, March 1, 1984.
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1950-1959; SERIES I (Box-folder 1)
  - NEWSLETTERS, 1946-1959; SERIES II (Box-folder 1)
  - CONFERENCES AND CONVENTIONS, 1946-1959, 1980; SERIES III (Box-folder 1-2)
  - LEGISLATIVE FILES, 1946-1982; SERIES IV (Box-folder 2-12)
  - CLIPPINGS, 1959-1961; SERIES V (Box-folder 13)
  - WASHINGTON STATE LABOR COUNCIL, EXECUTIVE BOARD, 1950-1959; SERIES VI (Box-folder 13)
    Contains minutes.
  - WESTON, EVAN M. (WSLC PRESIDENT), 1951-1959; SERIES VII (Box-folder 13)
    Contains correspondence.
  - DAVIS, JOSEPH H. (WSLC LEGISLATIVE REPRESENTATION), 1951-1979; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 13)
    Contains correspondence and minutes.
  - AFL-CIO POLITICAL EDUCATION COMMITTEE, WASHINGTON, 1958-1961, 1975; SERIES IX (Box-folder 13)
  - UNITED LABOR LOBBY, 1961-1963; SERIES X (Box-folder 13)
  - UNITED STATES PUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE, OCCUPATIONAL HEALTH DIVISION, WASHINGTON OCCUPATIONAL HEALTH SURVEY, ADVISORY COMMITTEE, 1961-1962; SERIES XI (Box-folder 13)
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council records, 1963-1983; 0450-007; 12 cubic feet 12 boxes
  Correspondence, legislative files, reports, newsletters, clippings, ephemera, other record series, 1963-1983.
  Bulk of the accession are papers of Louis O. Stewart, Educational Director of Washington State Labor Council Legislative files in this accession are all regarding Initiative 412 for Affordable Interest Rates on credit cards. Washington State Labor Council sponsored Initiative 412, which would lower interest rates and set a uniform method for determining rates.
  Gift of AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council, June 1, 1985.
  - LEGISLATIVE FILES REGARDING INITIATIVE 412 FOR AFFORDABLE INTEREST RATES, 1980-1983; SERIES I (Box-folder 1)
    Includes correspondence.
  - NEWSLETTERS, SERIES II
    - Washington State Labor Council AFL-CIO Reports, 1975 (Box-folder 1)
    - Washington State Labor Council Legislative Reporter, 1983 (Box-folder 1)
  - STEWART, LEWIS O. (WSLC EDUCATION DIRECTOR), 1968-1982; SERIES III (Box-folder 2-9)
    Includes correspondence and minutes.
  - DAVIS, JOSEPH H. (WSLC PRESIDENT), 1963-1980; SERIES IV (Box-folder 9-12)
  - WILLIAMS, MARVIN L. (WSLC PRESIDENT), 1977-1981; SERIES V (Box-folder 12)
  - RIEDER, ROSS K. (COORDINATOR, COPE COMPUTER PROJECT), 1975-1981; SERIES VI (Box-folder 12)
  - BISHOP, BRUCE A. (WSLC POLITICAL ACTION COORDINATOR), 1976-1977; SERIES VII (Box-folder 12)
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council records, 1938-1985; 1970-1985; 0450-008; 8 cubic feet 8 boxes
  Washington State Labor Council, Executive Board and committees' records
  Washington State Labor Council officers' papers
  Records of related organizations
  Correspondence, minutes, legislation, financial records, reports, newsletters, subject files, 1938-1985 (bulk 1970-1985). Also includes correspondence and other papers of Council President Marvin Williams, legislation of Elmer Kennedy. Of particular significance are materials relating to workers’ compensation from 1975 to 1980 and the minutes of the Council's Executive Board for the years 1981, 1984, and 1985
  AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council, August 20, 1986.
  - ORGANIZATIONAL RECORDS, SERIES I
    - Organizational Features, 1981, Undated (Box-folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 1941, 1970-1985 (Box-folder 1)
    - Minutes of Staff Meetings, 1983, 1985 (Box-folder 1)
    - Conferences and Conventions, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 1)
    - Financial Records, 1971-1984 (Box-folder 1)
    - Unemployment Compensation Files, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 2)
    - Reports, 1965-1977 (Box-folder 2)
    - Legislative Files, 1938-1948, 1984 (Box-folder 2-4)
    - Newsletters, 1946-1947, 1984 (Box-folder 4)
    - Subject Files, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 4-5)
  - WASHINGTON STATE LABOR COUNCIL, EXECUTIVE BOARD AND COMMITTEES, SERIES II
    - Executive Board, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 5)
      Includes correspondence; minutes; agenda; and other related files
    - Affiliation Committee, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 5)
    - Budget Committee, 1983, 1985 (Box-folder 5)
    - Training and Apprenticeship Committee, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 6)
    - Employment-Unemployment Committee, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 6)
    - Mass Transit Committee, 1985 (Box-folder 6)
    - Public Employees Committee., 1983-1985 (Box-folder 6)
    - Women's Committee, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 6)
      Includes correspondence; minutes; and other related files
  - WASHINGTON STATE LABOR COUNCIL OFFICERS, SERIES III
    - Williams, Marvin L. (President, 1980-1985) (Box-folder 6-7)
    - Kenney, Lawrence (Research Director), 1969-1979 (Box-folder 7)
  - RELATED ORGANIZATIONS, SERIES IV
    - AFL-CIO, Community Services Department, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 7)
    - United Labor Lobby, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 7)
      Includes minutes, 1983, 1985 and other related files.
    - Washington Employment and Training Council, 1982 (Box-folder 8)
    - Washington State Ferry Union Coalition, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8)
    - Welfare and Pension Administrative Service, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 8)
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council records, 1957-1985; 0450-009; 9 cubic feet 9 boxes
  Arranged in 5 series:
  Washington State Labor Council committees records
  AFL-CIO, Political Education Committee (COPE) records
  Organizational information, correspondence, minutes, financial records, speeches, conferences and conventions, subject files, 1957-1985. Includes Washington State Labor Council president Joe Davis's speeches 1957-1979, and president Marvin Williams's speeches, 1980-1982.
  Gift of AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council, October 23, 1987.
  - ORGANIZATIONAL RECORDS, SERIES I
    - Organizational Features, 1980-1984, Undated (Box-folder 1)
    - Financial Records - Reports of Auditors, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 1)
    - Financial Records - Budgets, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 1)
    - Newsletters, 1984 (Box-folder 1)
    - Elections, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 1)
    - Conferences and Conventions, 1966-1983 (Box-folder 1-2)
    - Activity Report, 1983 (Box-folder 2)